-早啊  -乌达查22号会去塔林
- Good morning. - UDC is going to be in Tallinn on the 22nd
我猜你慕尼黑的事情已经完成了
We're assuming you've finished whatever business you had in Munich?
差不多吧
That seems like a decent assumption.
埃利亚斯
Elias.
你知道在我给诺曼打电话后 他经历了什么吗
Do you know what happened to Norman after I called him?
他们来找他了
They came for him.
白俄罗斯发生的事有问题
Something went wrong in Belarus.
-诺曼知道我们要来  -如果有人泄密
- Norman knew we were coming. - If there's a leak,
这事必须要彻查 要解决掉
it has to be investigated and resolved.
从现在起 行动尽量保密
From here on, keep the circle tight.
我们过的这种生活不正常 你什么时候回来
This life, it's not normal. When are you coming back?
-我真的不知道  -太令人失望了 查尔斯
- Honestly, I don't know. - It's not good enough, Charles.
2号摄像头 实时画面
扩大追捕凶手范围
世界反应|英国外交大臣离开峰会 评论费斯特遇刺案
外交大臣 您对德国事件作何评价
Foreign Secretary. Can you comment on the events in Germany?
费斯特父子不仅是我的密友
Manfred and Elias Fest were not only close personal friends of mine,
他们更是西方价值观与社会的捍卫者
they were fearless defenders of Western values and our way of life.
您会是下一个吗 外交大臣
"Are you next, Foreign Secretary?
您是否担心您的安危
"Are you worried for your own safety?
这将给您的党派带来什么影响呢
"What does this mean for your party?"
莱克纳打来视频 德国联邦情报局有新进展
We have Leckner on video with an update from the BND.
失去他们这样的英雄 对德国
"The loss of these heroic men is a terrible tragedy for Germany,
德国人民 以及西方民主本身都堪称悲剧
"the German people, and for Western democracy itself.
再次感谢
"Thank you again."
英国外交大臣杰里米·怀特洛克
"The British Foreign Secretary, Jeremy Whitelock,
将费斯特父子的死
"calling the murders of Manfred and Elias Fest
称为西方民主本身的悲剧
"a tragedy for Western democracy itself.
全世界都在哀悼
"Around the world, tributes have..."
埃利亚斯·费斯特在几小时前遭谋杀
"Elias Fest was murdered a few hours ago
暂时不知道具体发生了什么
"and it will take time..."
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
但是有一件事很清楚
"However, one thing seems clear.
埃利亚斯·费斯特雇佣了一位职业杀手 去刺杀他父亲
"Elias Fest hired a professional assassin to kill his own father.
而且 很显然 他未能付清尾款
"Yeah, and apparently, he... he failed to pay what he owed."
恐怕他也没想到自己会被当成诱饵
He probably wasn't expecting to be used as bait.
杀手伪装成了轿车司机
"The assassin disguised himself as a limo driver
在埃利亚斯·费斯特前往葬礼路上枪杀了他
"and killed Elias en route to his father's funeral."
那我们是怎么得知的
And we know this, how?
埃利亚斯在车上时 正与他的安全总管穆勒通话
"Elias called his head of security er, Muller, from the limo."
-有通话录音吗  -没有
- Was the call recorded? - "Er, no."
-他们用德语交流吗  -没 英语
- Was it in German? - "Er, no, English."
杀手年龄
Age?
现在我只知道他是中年
"All I have at this time is not young, not old."
-有人看到他的脸了吗  -应该是没有
- Did anyone get a good look at him? - "It appears not, no."
你的调查怎么样了
"How are you getting on with your investigation?
那位英籍枪支制造者
"Your British gunmaker?"
我们正积极追查他哥哥这条线
We have a lead on his brother we're actively pursuing,
尽管我们目前并没查到多少
although right now I'm afraid we don't have anything
发送给麻雀：需要尽快见面
-值得分享的情报  -知道了
- significant enough to share. - "I see.
同时 杀手已经消失了
"Meanwhile our assassin has disappeared.
整个欧洲的警察都在寻找他
"Police all over Europe are looking for him."
梅斯  法国
混蛋 嘿
Putain! Hey!
瞧瞧 真是操蛋
该死
混蛋
Putain!
先生 对不起
你个白痴怎么开的车
非常抱歉 我的全责
你想要我赔你多少钱
你开着宝马 觉得钱能解决所有问题吗 混蛋
我老板会因为这件事找我麻烦
我一个月都白干了
瞧瞧
你月薪多少
我来赔
不不不
行不通
等警察来吧
我需要一份报告
他直接怼上了我的车屁股
请出示你们的证件
好啊
这是你的车吗
其实是租来的
他连车都不会开
请出示身份证件
好 我来了
都要吗
安东尼·马利森
Anthony Mallison?
对
给你
你在慕尼黑租的这辆车
是的
希望能快点解决这事
你在慕尼黑做什么
观光啊
慕尼黑很漂亮
你什么时候离开的
昨晚
让我看看你的后备箱
当然可以
把包打开
离车远一点
站后一点
是他的错 你也听他说了
别吵
接住
豺狼的日子
第一季 第四集
我的美国朋友选择冒险相信我
My American friend is taking a chance on me.
这不是与303的正式合作
It's not official for 303.
他们搜集到了一些聊天记录
They picked up some chatter.
罗丹的价格已达成一致 定金已付
"Rodin price point agreed. Commencement paid.
豺狼已在路上
"Jackal en route."
有人雇佣豺狼去杀另一个目标
Somebody's hiring the Jackal for another kill.
罗丹 你怎么看
Rodin? Mean anything to you?
可能是雇主
Could be the buyer?
更像是目标
More likely the target.
他们在哪搜集到的聊天记录
Where did they pick up the chatter?
他们不会说的
Wouldn't say.
比安卡 我们需要你尽快取得突破
We need a breakthrough Bianca, and soon.
南锡
梅斯
妈 不行
不能报警
但他有枪 阿尔瓦罗 他有枪
这不是你和你朋友能解决的事
是他 对吗
是他吗
嘿
Hey?
-嘿  -嗨
- "Hey." - Hi.
你还好吗
"Are you OK?"
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
所以
So, er...
我一直在思考你说的话
I've been thinking about what you said.
你说得非常对
"And I think you were absolutely right.
我太过分了
"I think this has all been too much."
是这样的 他们给我放了几天假
Look, they've got me away for a few more nights,
我就在想
but I was wondering
有没有可能我能说服你来巴黎
if there was any chance that I could persuade you to come to Paris.
-巴黎  -对
- Paris? - "Yeah."
我可以在巴黎马雷
"I thought I could try and get our room
给我们找个房间 就是孚日广场旁边那个
"at that little place in the Marais, the one by the Place des Vosges?
记得吗 我们可以在圣马丁订张桌子
"Remember? I thought we could try and get a table at the San Martin.
我们可以聊聊
"We could talk."
我不知道
I don't know.
有很多事
There's a lot that I...
我一直很害怕说
well, that I need to talk to you about...
但是我需要告诉你
...that I've been afraid to.
请一定要来
"Please come.
我看过航班了 有班两点从塞维利亚飞的飞机
"I checked the flights and there's a two o'clock from Seville."
求你了
Please.
好吧
Alright.
这是同意了 对吗
Was that a yes? Yeah, OK?
好的
OK.
我会把票和其他东西整理好 用邮件发给你
"I'll sort all the tickets and stuff, and I'll email you.
好
OK.
我爱你
I love you.
你从狙击手学院给的名单里查到什么了吗
Please tell me you've got something from Sniper School?
过去几周
None of the names from that list
那个名单上没有一个人出过国
have been out of the country in the past few weeks.
但其中可能有值得聊聊的人
But there might be one who's worth talking to.
乔治·汉兹 他管理着一个狙击手的群聊 他有点迷这个
George Hands. He runs a sniper WhatsApp group. He's obsessed.
-我现在就要和他聊  -不用
- I'm gonna go talk to him now. - Ah, no.
发我地址 我自己去
Text me the address. I'll go myself.
我不是内鬼
Hey, I'm not the mole, you know.
这也不是什么秘密
It's hardly a bloody secret, is it?
所有人都如履薄冰
Everyone's on edge.
卡弗请求访问所有知道白俄罗斯行动的人的手机和邮件
Carver's asking for access to phones and emails of anyone that knew about Belarus.
盯着点麻雀的手机 定位变了就通知我
Watch Sparrow's phone. If it moves, let me know.
-没想到是你  -对
- You're not what I was expecting. - Yeah.
经常这样 能进来吗
Get that all the time. Can I...?
3815米
3,815 metres?
知道有多远吗
Do you know how far that is?
不
No.
-超过两英里  -两英里
- That's over two of your English miles. - Two miles?
是吗
Is that right?
-知道子弹飞两英里要多久吗  -说说
- Do you know how long a bullet takes to travel two miles? - Tell me.
六七秒
Six, seven seconds.
就是说 你开枪时 目标还站在窗边
Like, your target can be standing by the window when you take that shot,
等子弹飞到 目标已经坐在马桶上了
and be sitting on the toilet by the time the bullet shows up.
你在这么远的距离开枪
You see, when you shoot at that distance,
考验的是你的预判
you are shooting into the future.
哇哦
Wow.
没错
Yeah.
那个人
Now, your fella...
或许他枪法不错
well, he's probably very good,
但他绝对是个撞大运的混蛋
but he is one lucky bastard, I tell you that.
他枪法不错
Well, if he's good...
那他一定曾在英国军队服役吧
he must be British Army, right?
绝对的
100 percent.
-你当年能射出那样一枪吗  -当然可以
- Could you have made that shot, back in the day? - Oh yeah, course.
轻轻松松
Standing on me head.
我以前枪法顶尖
Look, I was one of the best,
但两英里
but two miles?
我的射程没有这么远
I never took a shot at that range.
这上面的人 有谁能做到吗
Could anyone here have taken it?
威尔逊枪法太烂
That Wilson was a total wanker.
狙击准度差到离谱
He couldn't hit a barn door at ten yards.
帕克在蹲监狱
And Parker's in jail.
米切尔
Mitchell.
运气好的话
On a good day...
不行
...nah.
他确实不错
Nah. He was good.
但是不行 还是太远了
But, nah, it's just too far.
你那个群里肯定讨论得热火朝天
Must have been a lot of chat about this on your WhatsApp group.
那是当然 停不下来
Oh, course. Its nonstop.
群里有人能做到吗
Anyone in the group who could have made that shot?
等等
Hold on.
你
You?
怎么 你是说其中有人是嫌犯
What, are you saying they're suspects?
我只是在做一些背调
Oh, I'm just gathering some background.
他们中没人能做到
Cos none of the lads could've done it.
即使能 也不会做的
And even if they could, they wouldn't.
满意了
Yeah?
还你
Thanks.
干杯
Cheers.
在过去那些日子里
The good old days.
-我们是最顶尖的  -也不见得
- Now, we were the best. - Well, not really
毕竟你们谁也不能射中那一枪
cos none of you could've made that shot.
有一个人
There is one guy.
继续
Go on.
他曾在斯特灵前线训练营 是在我之后的人了
He was at Stirling Lines. It was after my time.
-他是个传奇  -谁
- But, well, he was a legend. - Who?
亚历山大·杜根
Alexander Duggan.
我在哪能找到他
And where can I find him?
首先你要飞去喀布尔
Well, first off, you need to take a plane to Kabul.
-喀布尔  -然后你得去赫尔曼德
- Kabul? - And then you get yourself down to Helmand.
你会就在拉什卡尔加找到杜根
And you'll find Duggan just outside Lashkar Gah.
他的碎片
Bits of him, anyway.
听说杜根和他队友都被炸死了
I heard Duggan was taken out by an IED with his entire squad.
真是糟糕
Messy.
这么说 杜根死了
So, Duggan's dead?
十年前的事了
Ten years ago.
谢谢
Thank you.
你帮了大忙
You've been so helpful.
不客气
You're welcome.
来电：比安卡
麻雀还没出酒店
The Sparrow hasn't moved from the hotel.
-汉兹说了什么  -给我把亚历山大·杜根的资料 统统找出来
- "What did Hands have to say?" - Get me everything you can on Alexander Duggan.
2013年死在赫尔曼德的狙击手
Sniper. Killed in Helmand in 2013.
为啥要找死人的资料
Well, what's the point, if Duggan's dead?
怎么说呢
Oh, my...
达米安 你去找就行 别问
Damian, please just do it! Fucking do it!
太棒了 查一个死人
Great. Searching for dead people.
巴黎  法国
你来了
Hi.
好
OK.
没订到马雷的房
Couldn't get our room in the Marais,
但我帮我们在圣马丁订到了一张桌子
but I did managed to get us a table at San Martin.
你有话想说 那就说吧 我听着
You said you wanna talk, so talk, or I go.
我要听真相
And I want the truth.
-不说我就走了  -我一直在骗你
- I go. - I've been lying to you since the day that I met you.
我爱你 努丽娅 我爱卡利托斯 这不假
I love you, Nuria, and Carlito. That's not a lie.
从来不假
And it never has been.
但如果我把我的真相告诉你
But I knew that if I told you the truth about myself...
我会失去你们
...then I'd lose you both.
真相是什么
What is the truth?
你是做什么的 查尔斯
What do you do, Charles?
我是个解决问题的人
I'm a trouble shooter.
具体点
What does that mean?
给大公司 跨国公司干活
So, big companies, multi-nationals,
他们要是遇到麻烦 就会派我去解决
when they have a problem, they send me in to solve it.
-遇到麻烦  -对
- A problem? - Yeah.
你杀人吗
Do you kill people?
不
No.
我不杀人
No, I don't kill people.
我是商业间谍
No. It's industrial espionage.
通常 这是公司竞争的潜规则
And, usually, it's relatively straightforward and above board.
有时 情况会稍微复杂一些
Occasionally, it's a little more complicated.
少部分时候 会触碰到法律的边界
And, erm sometimes, very rarely, it's illegal.
-违法吗  -有时 我会用假身份
- Illegal? - Sometimes I use false identities.
有时 我会贿赂别人
Sometimes I buy people off.
-听起来很危险啊  -我为那些亿万富豪工作
- Sounds fucking dangerous. - The people I work for are billionaires.
我调查的人也是亿万富豪 他们确实危险
The people I investigate are billionaires. They're all fucking dangerous.
那你儿子怎么办
What about your son?
-你什么意思  -不敢相信
- What'd you mean? - I can't...
不敢相信你一直把我们的生命置于危险之中
I can't believe you put our lives at risk.
没有 我从未把你们置于危险境地
Oh, no, I've never put your lives at risk.
努丽娅 我从未把你们置于危险中
Nuria, I've never put your lives at risk and-
你妻子 你儿子的身份
Just to be your wife, to be your son.
-会给我们带来危险  -听我说
- This is a risk for us. - Listen to me.
我非常谨慎 而且我擅长这个
I'm very careful, and I'm very good at what I do.
这些雇佣我的人并不完全了解我
Listen, these people that hire me they don't know anything about me,
-他们不知道我的名字  -你可能没意识到风险 查尔斯
- they don't know my name, and - Maybe you don't know the risk, Charles.
你说他们很危险 会威胁到我们
You say they are dangerous. Dangerous for us.
只需要几个星期 这些就能结束了
In a couple of weeks, this is all gonna be over.
这件事会告一段落 我保证 我受够了
It's gonna be done. I'm through. I meant that. I'm done with it.
只要做完这件事 我们就能有足够的钱
And once this job is done, we will have enough money
过我们向往的生活
to live the life that we wanna live.
-美好生活 努丽娅  -得了吧
- And it'll be a great life, Nuria. - Oh, come on.
-得了吧  -真的
- Come on. - It'll be a...
美好生活
It'll be a great life.
我们一家三口
The three of us.
一起生活
Together.
请相信我
Please believe me.
我怎么相信你
How can I believe you?
你对我说过谎
You lied to me.
从始至终 你都在骗我
From the start, you lie.
现在你却说
And now you say,
要我相信你 你要金盆洗手了
"Believe me, I don't want this anymore."
我该怎么相信你
How can I believe you?
告诉我
Tell me.
-怎么相信你  -我来这里
- How? - Because I'm here.
我来巴黎这个酒店
And the only reason that I'm here in Paris, in this hotel,
进这个房间的唯一原因 是我爱你
in this fucking room, is because my life is with you.
如果我
And if I don't...
失去你 我会一无所有
If I don't have that, then I don't have anything.
我喜欢你这样
I like you like this.
真情流露的模样
天哪
Oh, for fuck's sake.
你什么时候能完成工作
When do you finish this job?
两周
Two weeks.
之后 我向你保证
And then, I promise you,
会如你所愿
everything will be the way that you want it to be.
以后别骗我了
No more lies, please.
求你了
Please.
再也没有谎言
No more lies.
豺狼接什么任务都行
This Jackal is free to ply his trade. Fine.
纽约  美国
这就是自由经济
That's liberal economics,
但是杀了埃利亚斯·费斯特
but killing Elias Fest?
你有没有告诉豺狼
Did you, or did you not,
不要做任何可能威胁到我们项目的事
tell the Jackal not to do anything that would endanger our project?
我明确说了
I did. Explicitly.
那我们得找别人了
I think we need to find somebody else.
恕我直言 他在慕尼黑做的有什么不妥吗
With respect, did he go off piste in Munich?
我理解你的想法 但是时间不等人
Yes, I understand that, but time is short.
你不可能找到像豺狼这么专业的人
You're not gonna find anybody as good as the Jackal.
我可以从特种部队里找人
I can get someone from Special Forces like that.
你确实这么试过 但失败了
I understand you already went down that route and it didn't work out so well,
-所以利奥诺拉先来找我  -有新消息
- which is why Leonora came to me first. - I have an update.
原来是埃利亚斯雇了豺狼去杀曼弗雷德
Turns out Elias hired the Jackal to kill Manfred.
他没付钱 于是豺狼杀了他
He didn't pay up, so the Jackal killed him.
好吧 这真是恶心
OK, that's just sick.
-我们得停止与他合作  -等下
- We need to get shot of this guy. - Hang on.
豺狼为了讨债 折返慕尼黑 那里遍地是警察
This guy goes back to Munich, a town that is swarming with police, to call in an unpaid debt.
在我看来 这展现了他的品格
To me that speaks of character.
-他现在在哪  -应该在塔林
- Where is he now? - He should be in Tallinn.
你去找他 跟着他
You need to find him and stay with him.
好吧 这会很难办
Well, that would be challenging.
-他不会喜欢的  -我们因为你的推荐 才坚持选择豺狼
- He's not gonna like that. - We're sticking with the Jackal because you recommended it.
是你推荐的吗
Is that your recommendation?
是的
It is.
那你得负责
Well, on your head be it.
雕塑百科全书
罗丹
思考者是一尊由奥古斯特·罗丹创作的青铜雕塑 通常置于石座之上
雕塑描绘了一位坐在岩石上的裸体男性英雄形象 好似在沉思 常被用作象征哲学的形象
麻雀的手机定位还是没变
There's still no movement on Sparrow's phone.
好的
OK.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
我对你一见钟情
I've loved you since the first I saw you.
你就是我的唯一
You were the only girl for me.
这些年我在监狱里
And when I was in jail all those years...
你都支持着我
...you stood by me.
你每周都来看我
You came to visit me every week.
你总是在我身边
You were always there for me.
我们有过幸福时光
We had a great life.
麻雀：河边老地方 我们11点见
我会来的
我快到了
楼梯关闭
为了您的安全 施工期间严禁进入
这里是个人保护组
Personal Protection Unit.
请提供你的部门编号和个人身份号码
Can I have your department number and personal ID?
303521455B
"3-0-3-5-2-1-4-5-5-B."
是比安卡吗
Am I speaking to Bianca?
-对 是我  -你遇到危险了吗 比安卡
- "Yep, yep, you are." - Are you in danger, Bianca?
有个持刀男在追杀我
I'm being pursued by a man with a knife.
我正引着他去卡姆登洛克 北岸 高街南边
I'm leading him to Camden Lock, north bank, south of High Street.
我现在给你发定位
I'm sending you the pin now.
正在帮你连线 稍等
I'm connecting you now. Stand by.
定位附近的个人保护组特工
搜索范围
取消
搜索
搜索中
个人保护组 | 接线
姓名　　　　　　　　　文森特·派恩
部门编号　　　　　　　255
显示位置
返回
个人身份号码　　　　　348555R
-我是文森特·派恩  -比安卡·普尔曼遇到了危险
- This is Vincent Pyne. - "I have an officer in danger. Bianca Pullman.
-正在发送她的位置  -收到了
- "Sending you her location." - Received.
稍等
"Stand by."
比安卡 是我 文森特
"Bianca!? It's me, Vince.
-你具体在哪  -洛克莱德桥
- "Where exactly are you?" - Lockride bridge.
-你有危险吗  -是的 他有一把刀
- Are you in immediate danger? - "Well, he's has a knife,
他肯定想杀了我 但我不能杀他
"and he definitely wants to kill me, but I need this guy alive."
明白了 我们到达前 跟他保持距离
Understood. Keep your distance till we get there.
他还在追你吗
"Is he still on you?"
等下 他停下了
Hang on, he's stopped.
他为什么停下了
Why has he stopped?
糟了
Shit.
可恶
Fuck.
他跑了 不见了
He's gone. He's fucking gone.
我不能跟丢他 他是我唯一的线索
"I can't lose him, Vince. This guy's my only lead!"
好的 小心点 别挂电话
"OK, be careful. Stay on the line."
我看到他了 北岸 正朝南走
I've got him. North bank, heading south.
-我跟着他  -快到你那了 别做什么蠢事 好吗
- I'm going after him. - Almost with you. Don't do anything stupid, yeah?
拉里 站住
Larry! Larry stop!
放下刀
Drop the knife.
武装警察 武装警察
Armed Police! Armed Police! Armed Police! Armed Police!
站在原地 举起双手
Stay where you are! Stick your hands up!
-站在原地  -好久不见
- Stay where you are! - Hello, stranger.
拉里 趴下 放下武器
Larry, I need you to get on the floor and drop the weapon.
-拉里 放下  -别开枪
- Larry, drop the - Don't shoot!
可恶
Fuck.
武装警察 武装警察
Armed Police! Armed Police!
武装警察
Armed Police!
-她是谁  -我的线人
- Who the fuck is that? - She was my asset.
麻雀
Sparrow.
艾莉森
Alison.
直说吧 医生 她能挺过去吗
Give it to me straight, doctor. Is she gonna make it?
她会挺过去的
She'll pull through.
哦 我勇敢的战士
Oh, my brave soldier.
哦 去你的
Oh, fuck you.
一如既往的有魅力
Still charming as ever.
在个人保护组工作感觉怎么样
What's it like working in PPU?
我被借调了一年 等待下一个任务
I've been on secondment for a year. Waiting for my next assignment.
但还好 我喜欢保护其他人
But, you know, it's good. I like keeping people safe.
我可能要学学这方面的东西
Yeah, I might need some lessons in that.
做我们这行 总会有伤亡
You know how it is in this game, there's always casualties.
关键是尽量减少伤亡率
The trick is to keep them to a minimum.
拉里孤身一人在伦敦
And, look, Larry's alone in London.
警方觉得他们早晚能抓到他
The police are pretty certain they'll catch him sooner or later.
-都搞定了  -但是
- All done. - But...
有备无患
...better safe than sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
妈 你的胳膊怎么了
'Mum! What happened to your arm?'
妈
Mum?
怎么搞的
What happened?
-你还好吗  -我没事
- You alright? - Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
昨晚出了点事 但还好
It's been a night, but I'm good.
贾思敏 你去收拾上学的东西
Jaz, why don't you go and finish getting ready for school?
-我做了冰沙 你可以尝尝  -谢谢
- I made a smoothie if you want some. - Thank you.
你今天是要去爱丁堡
Oh, God, yeah it's, erm, Edinburgh today.
-格拉斯哥  -说错了 是去格拉斯哥
- Glasgow. - Glasgow, sorry.
您能告诉我发生了什么吗
So, can you tell me what happened?
不行
No.
好吧
OK.
每次你因为工作而消失
But when you disappear, for work,
真的很难不去想最坏的情况
it's really hard to not imagine worst-case scenarios.
真没你想的那么糟 我们能不能...
It's really not as bad as it looks. Can we just...
你这么说真让人心碎
And when you say things like that, it just shuts me out.
保罗 我们都清楚其中的道理
Paul, we both know how this thing runs?
-我们能不能...  -那我不去参加会议了
- Can we just... - OK, fine, well, then, I'll just not go to the conference.
-什么 我不是这个意思  -怎么不是了
- What, no, that's not what I'm... - Well, why not?
你为了这篇论文付出了很多
Listen, I know how hard you've worked on this paper.
-你得去参加会议  -爸 你会惊艳全场
- You are going. - Dad, you're gonna slay.
好吧 我会惊艳全场
OK, well, apparently, I'm gonna "slay," so...
拿好
Here.
别担心 好吗
You're good. OK?
好吧
OK, OK.
过来
Here.
-照顾好你母亲  -好
- Look after your mum, love. - Yeah.
再见
Bye.
你需要请假休息一下吗
Do you need to take some personal time?
不用 我没事 谢谢关心
No. No, I'm fine. Thank you.
那就好
Good.
有进展吗
Any new developments?
没有 目前没有
No. Not yet.
比安卡 我也想支持你
Bianca, I want to support you.
但最新情况是拉里逃跑了
But Larry escaping is only just the latest.
两名特工死在了白俄罗斯 一名线人被杀了
We have two field officers dead in Belarus, an asset murdered,
更别提这个线人的女儿还死在了拘留室
not to mention her daughter who died in custody.
并且现在 卡弗开始查每个人的手机和邮件
And now we have Carver going through everyone's phones and emails.
简直是一片狼藉
It's horribly messy,
不巧的是 这一切都因你而起
and, unfortunately, it all comes back to you.
上级现在很关注这件事
Oversight are already all over this.
我也想护着你 但我能做的有限
There's only so much I can do to protect you.
我们需要一些进展
We need to make some progress.
文森特·派恩
Vincent Pyne.
他和我一起在亨登受训
We trained at Hendon together.
他做过贴身保镖 高级驾驶员 战略顾问
He did close protection, advanced driver, tach adviser
之后加入了国家犯罪打击局 最后才来的军情六处
before he went to NCA and ended up at Six.
把他调到这个任务 协助我
I need him reassigned to this op.
我信任他 伊莎贝尔
I can trust him, Isabel.
好吧
Very well.
我尽力
I'll do my best for you,
但现在外交大臣在对我施压
but I am under a lot of pressure from the Foreign Secretary.
他要我们定期给他更新情况
He is asking me for regular updates.
所以 从此以后 你需要
So, from this point on, you need to tell me...
事无巨细地及时向我汇报
...every development the minute it happens.
-当然  -比安卡
- Of course. - Bianca...
事无巨细
every development.
我的新号码
-什么事  -诺曼 是我
- What? - "Norman, it's me."
我知道是你 要不然我也不会回电
I know it's you otherwise I wouldn't be calling you.
-你要什么  -我要个地址
- "What do you want?" - I need an address.
我问问我的人
I'll talk to my man.
来吧
Come on.
瓦尔马林岛 克罗地亚
我们收到消息 有人买凶要杀你
We have intelligence that a contract's been taken out on your life.
哦 是吗 基思
'Oh, really, Keith?'
当然有人要杀我
Of course a contract has been taken out.
难道你觉得既得利益者
Did we really think the Ancien Regime
会静静看着我发布资流吗
would stand idly by and let River flow?
先生 我得建议您不要离开这座岛
Sir, I have to recommend that you do not leave the island
直到这件事结束
until this is resolved.
我们必须去塔林参加发布会 如果我们现在取消
We have to be in Tallinn for the announcement. If we pull out now,
-对手可就要大做文章了  -您不能去塔林
- our enemies will have a field day. - You cannot go to Tallinn.
世界需要资流
The world needs River.
事关重大
It's bigger than all of us.
我们有理由相信 他们雇佣了一名职业杀手
We believe they've hired a professional assassin.
你从哪里得到的消息
Where are you getting this from?
情报界的可靠消息来源
Credible sources within the intelligence community.
是谁买凶
Who's taken out this contract?
-我们不知道 先生  -杀手叫什么
- We don't have that information, sir. - Does the assassin have a name?
不知道
Unknown to us.
所以 你不知道谁想杀他
So, you don't know who wants him dead,
也不知道会是谁来动手
and you don't know who's taking the shot.
但你想叫停这一有历史意义的发布会
But you want to call off an event of this historic magnitude?
查尔斯先生在塔林不安全
Mr Charles will be extremely vulnerable in Tallinn.
你负责他的安保 去保证他的安全
You're his security. Make sure he's secure,
让乌达查做好乌达查
and let UDC be UDC.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
让乌达查做好乌达查
"Let UDC be UDC."
他肯定喜欢
He'll love it.
四号无人机已起飞 开始传输信号
"Drone four airborne and transmitting."
塔林  爱沙尼亚
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉
Sorry.
没关系 我得搜下你的身
No worries. I'm just gonna have to pat you down.
手臂抬起来 可以把手臂伸展开吗
Raise your arms. Could you put your arms out?
哦我知道了 可能是这个
Do you know what? It's probably... It's probably that.
哦 没事 您可以带钱包
Oh, well you're allowed to have your wallet.
我得扫一下你身上
Just gonna check.
没问题
All clear.
-太好了 嗯  -您的手机
- All good. Yeah. - Here's your phone.
-谢谢你  -尽情享受吧
- Oh, thank you. - Enjoy the concert.
我会的
I will.
第一阶段开始 打开隔音墙
无酒精啤酒
One non-alcoholic beer.
你变了
You changed.
对
Yeah, um... Yeah.
我得到的消息说
'So, I've been given some information.'
豺狼又接了一单
The Jackal's been contracted for another hit.
-目标是谁  -我只知道代号
- Who's the target? - All I have is a codename
-罗丹  -你不知道是谁
- Rodin. - You don't know who it is?
-目前还不知道  -伊莎贝尔怎么说
- No. Not yet. - What's Isabel say?
我还没告诉她
I haven't told her-
你还没告诉你领导 什么情况
You haven't told your boss? What the fuck?
我不知道还能信任谁 文森特
I don't know who I can trust right now, Vince.
特别是在白俄罗斯行动之后
Especially after Belarus.
所以 有哪些人事前知道白俄罗斯的行动
So, who knew about Belarus?
303里
In 303...
达米安 欧斯
Damian, Osi,
当然还有伊莎贝尔
Isabel, obviously.
卡弗已经在调查了
Carver's on the job now,
现在是地毯式找内鬼
so it's a full-blown mole hunt.
罗丹的事情你准备怎么办
What you gonna do about Rodin?
我也不知道啊
I don't know, man.
如果连组织都不能相信 我怎么找到这个人呢
How am I supposed to find this man if I can't trust my organisation?
是啊
Yeah.
听起来糟透了 朋友
Sounds like you're fucked, mate.
-是吗  -所以 咱们好好喝一杯
- Really? - So, why don't we get you a proper drink,
点几杯鸡尾酒 一些烈酒
get a few cocktails, maybe some shots.
我得回去照顾女儿 她一个人在家
Erm... I've gotta get back to my daughter, she's on her own.
-保罗呢  -他出差去了
- Where's Paul? - He's on a work trip.
怎么样
How's that going?
-你说出差  -我说你们的婚姻
- The work trip? - The marriage?
-挺好的  -挺好的
- It's good. - "Good."
你们在一起都聊什么啊
What do you guys even talk about?
大学老师和爱玩枪的人
A college professor and a gun nut?
-很多话题啊  -比如
- Lots of stuff. - Like what?
就一些事嘛
Stuff.
一些事
"Stuff."
闭嘴
Shut up.
打开声罩 四 三 二
操
Fuck.
Fuck!
操
有人把手机交过来吗
这里没有
抱歉 没有人捡到手机
I'm sorry. No-one's handed a phone in.
-糟了  -嗯
- Oh, fuck. - Yeah.
那部手机很重要
I need that phone.
-我们的手机都很重要  -是啊
- Well, we all need our phones. - Yeah.
好吧 谢谢你
Yeah, OK. Thank you.
等等 跟我来
You know what? Erm, come with me.
你给我下电话号码
I'm gonna need your number.
-好 我直接输吗  -好 你输吧
- Yeah, shall I put it in? - Yeah. Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
-输好了  -谢谢
- There you go. - Thanks.
哦 找到了
Oh. Jackpot.
太棒了
Encouraging.
哦 我看到了
Oh, I see something.
-给您  -哦 太好了
- Here it is. - Oh, yeah.
你救了我一命 太感谢你了
You are a hero. Thank you so much.
-不用客气  -你叫什么
- You're welcome. - What's your name?
-拉斯穆斯  -拉斯穆斯
- Erm, Rasmus. - Rasmus.
谢谢你 拉斯穆斯
Thank you, Rasmus.
我叫彼得
I'm Peter.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
有人吗
Hello?
啊 天呐 贾思敏
Ah, God. Jasmine!
贾思敏
Jaz?
你这个母亲做得也太差劲了吧
What kind of mother are you?
我和贾思敏在这等了你好几个小时
Me and Jasmine have been waiting for hours.
我要让你亲眼见证
I want you to see this.
你还好吗 我看看 你没事
You OK? Show me. You're OK, you're OK.
给 拿上这个 快跑
Here, take this. Go. Go.
告诉我诺曼在哪
You're gonna tell me where Norman is. Right now.
-操你  -操我
- Fuck you. - Fuck me?
这里是我家
You're in my house!
我问你答
Tell me everything I need to know.
不然我在这杀了你
Or you die. Right here.
动手吧
Go ahead.
Do it.
妈
Mum!
拉斯穆斯　+372 89076 4937　保存联系人
拉里·斯托克 你被捕了 罪名是非法监禁
Larry Stoke, you're arrested for force imprisonment
以及严重的故意伤人
and intent to cause grievous bodily harm.
你可以保持沉默 但可能会影响辩护
You do not have to say anything, but it may harm your defence...
他说你杀了他女儿
He said you killed his daughter.
当然没有
Of course not.
没事吧
Cool.
你好
Hello.